Became Medicare game or platform development?
It is a reduced the set of Android release provided to chipset vendors and OEMs before a new Android
platform is released.
The goal of creating a release is to help chipset vendors and OEMs to migrate to a new place.
So the So The Folder PDK contains just the platform development it will release includes only necessary
components for developing Android L stands for hardware.
Absolutely.
Note that the full Android release is a superset of BTK release, and there is no separate public release
to public as the full platform release includes everything in the game.
So the build the folder within the BTK is a place holder for BTK build related stuffs and apps, folder
and system of some apps.
So in the BTK folder, there is this build folder, which actually consists of the BTK and in the Apps
folder, there'll be some next steps and there is also your tool folder.
So at the moment, it contains only some items scripts.
These folder is given to the OEMs or the chipset vendors to start some parallel development of hardware
abstraction layers.
So at the moment, the contents of this BTK folder is not that interesting for us.
The next we have the platform boasting folder for the platform, testing on tests of the platform test
modules.
So you can read more about the platform testing in this link.
Source code Android or Chrome compatibility tests.
So within a hospital, you can find the platform testing for the here and under which there is a test
folder.
In this, you can see a lot of unit tests like assembly.
If you take automotive to functional, then this is some unit test related to the lab grade and then
if you open this.
These are simple units that are ninja unit, and you can find two different different modules here,
like the Dialer on lock screen, media center, etc. These are functional test.
And then there are some health tests.
Again, great Niall.
Google Play.
And similarly, there are many other Jhang tests here.
You can see some Chang does.
What are the dialer?
So this folder consists of lot of tests, and in the utils you can find some utilities and there are
some libraries.